大家欢迎 "粉雄救兵"联合主持人 Karamo Brown
Karamo Brown, everybody, co-host of "Queer Eye."
同时他也是位心理医生 刚出版了一本自传
He's a psychotherapist. Got a new book out,
"Karamo: My Story of Embracing Purpose, Healing, and Hope"
"Karamo: My Story of Embracing Purpose, Healing, and Hope."
？？Karamo Brown "粉雄救兵" 文化专家
-欢迎来到节目 玩得开心  -好的
-Welcome to the show. Let's have a good time.  -Yes.
来吧 大家 开始"对战"
Come on, y'all! Let's play "Feud"!
？？Karamo队
有请Terry 有请Karamo
Give me Terry. Give me Karamo.
我的兄弟 我的兄弟 你好
My man, my man. Whoo.
-现在两清了 伙计  -老兄
-That's clean now, boy.  -Oh, man.
好了 开始了 伙计们
All right, let's go, fellas.
屏幕上有7个答案
Top seven answers on the board.
这是个填空游戏
This is a fill-in-the-blank.
我们问了100位单身女性
We asked 100 single women,
"在一个疯狂的派对上 有个人想对我的脚怎么样"
"At a wild party, some guy tried to blank my feet."
-亲吻  -亲吻
-Kiss.  -Kiss.
-我们先玩 我们先玩  -你们先玩
-We gonna play. We gonna play.   -You gonna play.
好了 Jason 填空
All right, Jason. Fill in the blank.
我们问了100位单身女性
We asked 100 single women,
"在一个疯狂的派对上 有个人想对我的脚怎么样"
"At a wild party, some guy tried to blank my feet."
？？Jason Brown Karamo的儿子
我想说 我曾是这事的受害者 吸吻
I'm gonna say, 'cause I've been the victim of this, suck.
我不想知道具体信息
Information I did not want to know.
-吸吻脚趾  -太棒了
-Sucking toes!  -Yes!
好了 Ian 填空
All right, Ian. Fill in the blank.
问了100位单身女性
Talked to 100 single women.
？？Ian Jordan Karamo的未婚夫
"在一个疯狂的派对上 有个人想对我的脚怎么样"
"At a wild party, some guy tried to blank my feet."
-舔  -舔 好
-Lick.  -Lick. Yeah.
好样的 好答案 好答案
Yeah, good answer, good answer.
-太棒了  -干得漂亮
-Yes!  -Good job.
好了 Kamilah 开始填空
All right, Kamilah, let's go. Fill in the blank.
我们问了100位单身女性
We asked 100 single women,
"在一个疯狂的派对上 有个人想对我的脚怎么样"
"At a wild party, some guy tried to blank my feet."
？？Kamilah Brown Karamo的姐姐
-按摩  -按摩
-Massage.  -Massage.
-好回答  -很棒
-That's a good one.  -That's good.
太棒了
Yeah!
好了 Charmaine 开始填空
All right, Charmaine. Here we go. Let's fill in the blank.
我们问了100位单身女性
We asked 100 single women,
"在一个疯狂的派对上 有个人想对我的脚怎么样"
"At a wild party, some guy tried to blank my feet."
-挠我的脚  -挠 好的
-Tickle my feet.  -Tickle. Yeah.
好样的
Yeah!
很嗨啊 这里有个迷人的小家庭
We rolling here. We got the little sexy family over here.
Karamo 填空 兄弟
Karamo, fill in the blank, man.
我们问了100位单身女性
We asked 100 single women,
"在一个疯狂的派对上 有个人想对我的脚怎么样"
"At a wild party, some guy tried to blank my feet."
-闻  -闻
-Smell?  -Smell.
-太棒了  -我们做到了 你做到了 你做到了
-Yeah!  -We got it! You got it, you got it.
还剩一个答案 Jason
One answer left, Jason.
来吧 再给我个
Come on, give me something for you, too.
我们问了100位单身女性
We asked 100 single women,
"在一个疯狂的派对上 有个人想对我的脚怎么样"
"At a wild party, some guy tried to blank my feet."
我想说 涂
I'm gonna go with paint.
-涂  -是的 涂抹
-Paint?  -Yeah. Uh, like, uh, paint.
-脚指甲  -这样啊 理解错了
-Oh, toenails.  -So, there you go. Got it wrong.
不错嘛 涂
That ain't bad. Paint!
没事的 没事
That's all right. It's all right, it's all right.
好了 Ian 还剩一个答案
All right, Ian, one answer left,
但只有一次机会
but you got only one strike.
我们问了100位单身女性
We asked 100 single women,
"在一个疯狂的派对上 有个人想对我的脚怎么样"
"At a wild party, some guy tried to blank my feet."
-踩  -踩
-Step on.  -Step on.
来到第二道题
Let's go to Question 2.
有请Rebecca 有请Jason
Give me Rebecca. Give me Jason.
开始了 屏幕上有6个答案
Here we go. Top six answers on the board.
我们问了100位已婚男士
We asked 100 married men,
说出一件你妻子不会和你分享的东西
name something your wife refuses to share with you.
-她的巧克力  -她的巧克力
-Her chocolate.  -Her chocolate.
好样的
Yeah!
-我知道的 对吗 女士们  -她知道
-I know. Right, ladies?  -She knows.
我永远也想不到
I would've never got that.
你们都在那欢呼
And all y'all were "yay!"
问了100位已婚男士
Talked to 100 married men.
说出一件你妻子不会和你分享的东西
Name something your wife refuses to share with you.
？？Azriel Crews Terry的女儿
-洗漱用品  -洗漱用品
-Toiletries?  -Toiletries.
好了 Tera 我们问了100位男士
All right, Tera. We asked 100 men,
说出一件你妻子不会和你分享的东西
name something your wife refuses to share with you.
？？Tera Crews Terry的女儿
-钱  -好回答
-Money.  -That's good.
很棒 Tera 很棒 Tera
That's good, Tera. That was good, Tera.
-屏幕上没有的别先说  -钱
-Don't say that until it's on the board.   -Money!
-有希望获胜 Tera  -太对了
-Got us in, Tera.  -That is so true.
好了 Anna女士 开始吧
All right, Ms. Anna, here we go.
我们问了100位已婚男士
We talked to 100 married men.
说出一件你妻子不会和你分享的东西
Name something your wife refuses to share with you.
？？Anna Mae Parks Rebecca的妈妈
-她的内衣  -她的内衣
-Her underwear.  -Her underwear.
-我的天  -是的
-Oh, my God!  -Yeah.
-有充分理由  -内衣
-For good reason.  -Underwear!
太棒了
Yeah!
？？Crews队
Terry 100位已婚男士
Terry, 100 married men,
说出一件你妻子不会和你分享的东西
name something your wife refuses to share with you.
她的车
Her car.
？？Crews队
她不让我开 总是说 "不行"
She won't let me. It's like, "Unh-unh."
是你送她的礼物吗
Did you give it to her as a gift?
我作为礼物送给她的
I gave it to her as a gift.
-你却不能开  -我不能开
-And you can't drive it?  -And I can't drive it.
-那不是错误的选择吗  -是的 我懂
-Ain't that a trip?  -Ain't it. I know!
她的车
Her car!
不
Oh, no!
什么
What?!
还剩两次机会 Rebecca 得小心了
Two strikes, Rebecca. We got to be careful.
Karamo队能偷分的
Team Karamo can steal.
说出一件你妻子不会和你分享的东西
Name something your wife refuses to share with you.
被子
The bed covers.
-被子  -被子
-The covers.  -The covers!
很棒 很棒 里面有 肯定有
That's good. That's good. We in there, we in there!
被子
The bed covers.
-太棒了  -太棒了
-Yeah!  -Yeah!
谢谢你 宝贝 谢谢你 宝贝 你救了我们 谢谢
Thank you, baby. Thank you, baby. You saved it. Thank you.
Azriel 两次机会 得小心了
Azriel, two strikes. We got to be careful.
Karamo家庭能偷分的
Karamo family can steal.
她的身体
Her body?
-我的天啊  -我不知道
-Oh, my God.  -I don't know.
不会分享她的身体
Oh, well. Won't share her body.
好了 我们问了100位已婚男士
All right, we asked 100 married men,
说出一件你妻子不会和你分享的东西
name something your wife refuses to share with you.
牙刷
Toothbrush.
-那会让我很恶心  -牙刷
-That would gross me out.  -Toothbrush!
我们成功了 成功了
We got it? We got it!
We got it! We got it all!
第三个答案
Number 3.
盥洗室
The bathroom.
这是实话
Ooh, ain't that the truth.
第二个答案
Number 2.
秘密或幻想
Secrets/fantasies.
目标是300分 别走开
The goal is 300 points, so don't go away.
"名流家庭对抗" 稍后回来
We'll be back with "Celebrity Family Feud."
欢迎回到 "名流家庭对抗" 观众们
Welcome back. "Celebrity Family Feud," everybody.
？？Karamo队
？？Crews队
有一队很出色 Karamo队得到了97分
We got a good one. Team Karamo got 97.
Crews家庭得到了52分
Crews family got 52.
有请Azriel 有请Ian
Give me Azriel. Give me Ian.
来吧 Ian
Come on, Ian!
-你好  -你好
-Hi.  -Hi.
我去 双倍分数
Damn. Point values are double.
屏幕上有5个答案 祝你们好运
We got the top five answers on the board. Good luck.
说出一件匹诺曹放在包里
Name something that Pinocchio carries in his backpack
说谎后用来削鼻子的东西
to shorten his nose after he lies.
说吧
Shoot!
-卷笔刀  -卷笔刀
-Pencil sharpener.  -Pencil sharpener.
Tera
Tera.
一个指甲刀 指甲刀
A nail file. A nail file.
-你刚才是想按铃吗  -是的 她想按
-Did you just try to hit the buzzer?  -Yeah. She did.
-不是  -我叫"Tera" 然后她
-That did not...  -Tera said, I said, "Tera," she...
一个指甲刀
A nail file!
太棒了
Yeah!
Kamilah 给我上面的一个答案
Kamilah, one answer to top it.
-一把锯子  -一把锯子
-A saw.  -A saw.
？？Karamo队
好了 Charmaine女士
All right, Lady Charmaine.
说出一件匹诺曹放在包里
Name something Pinocchio carries in his backpack
说谎后用来削鼻子的东西
to shorten his nose after he lies.
-一把刀  -一把刀
-A knife.  -A knife.
太棒了
Yeah!
Karamo 说出一件匹诺曹放在包里
Karamo, name something Pinocchio carries in his backpack
说谎后用来削鼻子的东西
to shorten his nose after he lies.
-一件用来掩盖的围巾  -一件用来掩盖的围巾
-A handkerchief to hide it?  -A handkerchief to hide it.
没事
That's okay.
Jason 只有一次机会
Jason, only one strike.
说出一件匹诺曹放在包里
Name something Pinocchio carries in his backpack
说谎后用来削鼻子的东西
to shorten his nose after he lies.
其实我想说白蚁
I was actually gonna say termites.
懂我意思吗 把它们放在那 然后就
Know what I mean? Just getting them on there, they just...
这是我兄弟
This is my dude, right here.
白蚁
Termites.
没事 但是个好答案
That's all right. Good answer, though.
好了 Ian 有两次机会
All right, Ian. We got two strikes.
得小心了 伙计 Crews家庭能偷分
You got to be careful, buddy. The Crews family can steal here.
-一个木槌  -一个木槌
-A mallet.  -A mallet.
好吧
Okay.
-没事的 没事  -敲下去
-That's all right. That's all right.  -Pound it down.